边境杀手2：边境战士
每年 都有成千上万的人
在美墨边境被偷渡到美国谋取利益
墨西哥的边境输送由贩毒集团控制
德州 美墨边境
这是奥马哈4-4 现在拉雷多方向158
Guardian, this is Omaha 4-4 on heading 158 to Laredo.
收到 奥马哈4-4
Copy, Omaha 4-4.
热成像能清晰 看到他们在移动
I'm picking up movement on the FLIR.
我们再靠近一些
Coming in for a closer look. Stand by.
这是美国边境巡逻队
This is the United States Border Patrol.
跪下 举起你们的双手
Get on your knees and put your hands up.
-嘿！趴下！
-我说英语
Hey! Get down!I speak English.
-趴下！
I speak English.Get down!
趴下！
Stay down!
Get down!
美国边境巡逻队
This is the United States Border Patrol.
跪下来 双手放在头上
Get on your knees and put your hands on your head.
这是美国边境巡逻队
This is the United States Border Patrol.
跪下 举起你的手
Get on your knees. Put your hands up.
美国边境巡逻队
This is the United States Border Patrol.
把手放在头顶！
Let me see your hands!
把手放在头顶！ 把手放在头顶！
Show me your hands! Show me your hands!
把手放！
Show...!
请注意
Be advised.
发生爆炸
There's been an explosion.
有警员倒地受伤
Officers are down.
嘿！在这里！
Hey! Over here!
找到了什么？
What do you got?
祈祷毯
Prayer rugs.
堪萨斯城
亲爱的 是的
Hey, honey. Yeah.
和我一起待在这里
Stay here with me. Just stay here.
没事的
It's okay.
跟我一起慢慢的走
Just come with me slowly and quietly.
跟我待在一起 天啊
Stay here with me. Stay... Oh, God.
你不要这么做
You don't have to do this.
别这么做 求你了
You don't have to do this, please.
今晚的堪萨斯城充满了
The scene in Kansas City tonight
恐惧、困惑和悲伤
is one of horror, confusion and grief.
15个伤亡者其中有两个孩子
15 people, among them two children,
到目前为止已经确认死亡
还有更多的人受伤 .
are so far confirmed dead with many more injured...
受害者家属依然在现场哭喊
The victims' families remain...
监视器画面中显示攻击者
Haunting images of the attackers
令人难以置信的袭击行为
are coming to light from surveillance...
国防部长詹姆斯莱利
Secretary of Defense James Riley
将对袭击事件发表声明
is expected to make a statement on the attacks.
我们高度关注事件进展并救助伤者
Our intense focus on recovery and assisting the injured
以及那些在事件中失去亲人的民众
and the families of those who have been killed
我们要坚定意志 并有决心
is matched only by our determination
防止更多可能的恐怖攻击
to prevent more attacks.
我们想对这些恐怖份子说
A message to our attackers.
你的炸弹不会吓倒我们
Your bombs do not terrify us.
它们赋予我们力量
They empower us.
我们将会加倍奉还
They empower us to send you something
令你们胆寒的：
that is truly terrifying:
美国军队的全部武力
the full weight of the United States military.
索马利亚海湾
趴下 趴在地上！
Down, down, down on the ground!
为什么抓我？
No! Here for what?!
我不是战士！
I'm not the f-fighter!
战士！
Fighter!
纳慕尔营地 吉布地
还好吗？
How you doing?
你觉得我是要对你用水刑吗 巴希米尔？
You think I'm gonna waterboard you, Bashiir?
水刑是我们不能虐待时才用
Waterboarding is when we can't torture.
这是非洲
This is Africa.
我他妈的可以为所欲为
I can do whatever the fuck I want here.
你得回答我问你的每一个问题
You're gonna answer every question I ask you
而且不用我伤你一根毫毛
without me harming a hair on your head.
知道为什么吗？
Do you want to know why?
因为如果你不
Because if you don't...
我只要打通电话 你家就会被空袭
...I'm gonna call in an air strike on your house.
还有 游泳池真不赖
Nice pool, by the way.
犯罪怎么会没有代价
Whoever said crime doesn't pay
你以为不抢油轮就没事？
wasn't stealing oil tankers, were they?
那些人是叶门人
Those men are Yemeni.
我们和那事毫无关系
We have nothing to do with that.
你们要找的是伊斯兰国 而不是我
Your fight is with ISIS, not me.
我们只在海上打仗
All my fights are on water.
当然了 巴希米尔
They sure are, Bashiir.
说到叶门？
And Yemen?
就在海湾对面
Just across the gulf.
真巧啊
What a coincidence.
现在如果叶门的民族主义者
It's kind of tricky for Yemeni nationalists
想预定个国际航班去美国 谈何容易？
to book an international flight these days, huh?
所以 假设他们能拿着假护照 蒙混过关
So, if their passports were fake,
直接就飞到了堪萨斯城
they'd fly straight to Kansas City
而不是去100多英里外的墨西哥
instead of going to Mexico and hiring coyotes to truck them
去雇用偷渡车来运送他们 是吧？
a hundred miles to the desert, right?
所以 最大的问题是：
他们是怎么到墨西哥的？
So, the big question is: how'd they get to Mexico?
因为他们铁定不能搭飞机
'Cause they sure as hell didn't fly.
所以 他们是坐船到达墨西哥的
No, they... traveled by ship.
一艘你没去抢劫的船
A ship you didn't try and steal.
这代表有人付钱 叫你别抢
So that means someone paid you not to.
所以我唯一的问题 巴希米尔
So, here's my only question, Bashiir.
谁付钱给你 让船安全通过的？
Who paid you to let the ship through?
那是你的兄弟吗？
Is that your brother?
因为我不想措杀了泳池管理员
'Cause I don't want to kill the pool guy.
每一艘船都在走私人口
Every ship smuggles people.Mm-hmm.
他们不需要我的许可
And they don't need my permission.
是的 他们他妈的需要
Yes, they fucking do.
最后的机会
Last chance.
你是在吓唬我
This is a bluff.No.
你是美国人
You American.
你有太多规则要遵守
You have too many rules.[DIALING]
今天没有规则 下个命令就行
No rules today, sport, just orders.
干吧 你可以行动了
DISPATCHER: Go ahead, sir.You're green.
收到
DISPATCHER: Roger that.
不要
No, no, no, no, no.
你得好好看着
No, I want you to watch it. I want you to watch it.
看着
Watch.
你有一个大家庭 巴希米尔
You have a big family, Bashiir.
很多兄弟
Lots of brothers.
你应该选择另一种工作
You should've chosen another line of work.
我可以这样搞上一整天都
I could do this all day.
但迟早
But sooner or later,
我会搞到你连一个兄弟都没有
I'll get the brother you can't live without.
我保证
I promise.
还有一件事情指向
It's one more thing
马塔莫罗斯贩毒集团
pointing to the cartels.
现在这些钱来自于
卡西姆阿尔-雷米的营地
Now, the money came from Quassim Al-Raymi's camp,
这倒不令人意外
which isn't a surprise.
另一方面 这艘船
The ship, on the other hand,
是一艘巴拿马货轮 拉维托利纳号
is a Panamanian freighter, La Victorina,
注册于墨西哥控股公司杜罗集团名下
registered to the Mexican holding company Grupo Duro.
它于18日停靠在韦拉克鲁斯港
It docked at Port of Veracruz on the 18th.
卡洛斯雷耶斯的公司
Carlos Reyes' company.
仅此一艘
The one and only.
如果你需要麦特回国
If you need Matt home,
我明早六点就能把他送回去
I can get him out at 0600 tomorrow.
我现在要飞去华盛顿
I'll have a plane to Washington
一小时后飞机准备好
ready for you in an hour.
明天见 麦特
See you tomorrow, Matt.[LINE CLICKS]
偷渡恐怖份子
在我看来 是很短视的行为
Smuggling terrorists seems pretty short-sighted to me.
边境现在查的很紧
Border's gonna tighten like a vice now.
911之后古柯碱的价格怎么样 肯？
What happened to the price of cocaine after 9/11, Ken?
紧绷的边界对偷渡生意有好处
Tight borders are good for business.
麦卡伦 德州边境
我们走吧
Let's go.
你3点前回家 好吗？
Will you be home by 3:00?
我得在科学展览会上待到很晚
I have to stay late for the science fair.
要我去接你吗？
Do you want me to pick you up?
我坐公车 好的
I'll take the bus. Okay.
我们走吧
Let's go.
非常好
It's pretty good.
他们一天赚多少？
How much they make?
把风吗？
For lookout?
20 30元一天吧
20, 30 a day.
表弟 他们就值这么多了
Man, but that's all they're worth.
但是你
But you...
你熟悉这条河的两边
well, shit, you know both sides of the river.
你有护照 来去自如
You got a passport. Come and go as you please.
拉法！
Rafa!
把我介绍给你表妹 混蛋
免谈 宅男
你认识他？
是的
Eh.
他表妹屁股很大 翘臀
发生了什么事？
What's going on?
把啤酒藏起来
Hide the beer.
你可以自己出个价 知道吧
You can name your own price, you know.
怎样？
Hmm?
这是边境
This is the border.
马塔莫罗斯贩毒集团
给大家提供了很好的工作赚钱机会
The Matamoros Cartel pay people well to work it.
你可以
You can, uh...
和我一起发财吧 表弟
start making your earn with me, cousin.
拿着
Take it.
这是你的
It's yours.
那么我该怎么做？
So, what do I have to do?
麦特 你真的应该涂点防晒乳
You really ought to invest in a little sunscreen, Matt.
如果你们在多云的地方发动战争
If you guys would start wars someplace cloudy,
我就不需要了
I wouldn't have to.
司法部确认了其他自杀式炸弹袭击者的身份？
DOJ get an ID on those other suicide bombers?
还没有 可能还正调查
Not yet.Uh, might want to get on that.
有证据显示雷耶斯贩毒集团
There's proof Reyes Cartel
帮助他们其中的一人到达边境 所以
helped one of them get to the border, so...
我们知道的 足以进行下一步
we know enough to move forward.
部长先生
Mr. Secretary...
麦特 格拉弗
Matt Graver.
坐吧
Have a seat.
你认为对于跨越我们国界的
贩毒集团来说
What do you think is the most valuable commodity
最有价值的商品是什么？
that cartels move across our borders?
20年前 古柯碱
20 years ago, cocaine.
今天我得说是人
Uh, today I'd have to say it'd be people.
这是一种他们不需要培养或处理的资源
It's a resource they don't have to cultivate or process
就算一次没有越境成功
and if they don't make it across,
他们可以再次付钱重来
they can pay to cross again
价格行情是一公斤货得的三倍
at three times the price of a kilo.
你如何定义恐怖主义 格拉弗先生？
How would you define terrorism, Mr. Graver?
我想这是你的工作 先生
I think that's your job, sir.
目前的定义是"任何个人或团体"
The current definition is "Any individual or group
用暴力来达到一个政治目的
that uses violence to achieve a political goal."
政府现在认为
The administration believes that
贩毒集团很符合这个定义
the drug cartels now fit that definition.
下个星期 总统将把贩毒集团
Next week, the president's adding drug cartels
也列入恐怖组织的名单
to the list of terrorist organizations.
你可以理解成这可以增加
You can understand how that will
我们打击他们的强度
expand our ability to combat them.
贩毒恐怖集团之间
The cartel territories
现在算是相当稳定
are fairly stable at the moment,
但正如我们在伊拉克学到的
but as we learned in Iraq,
如果能让他们鹬蚌相争
striking your enemy is a whole hell of a lot easier
我们就更容易打击他们
if they're fighting each other.
你需要什么 我就做什么
I'll do whatever you need.
给我指条路就行
Just point the way.
你有什么想法吗？
Do you have any thoughts?
我的意思是 我不会干掉一个贩毒集团头目
I mean, I wouldn't take out a cartel leader.
然后把一个贩毒集团分裂成50个
Turn one cartel into 50.
再说 杀死国王
并不会发动毒贩之间战争 而是结束
Besides, killing kings doesn't start wars, it ends them.
那是我们的事
That's our concern.Mm-hmm.
你有雷耶斯的具体位置吗？
You have a location on Reyes?
没有 但我们正在监控他的家庭
No, but the family's under surveillance.
他和他们之间有联络吗？
Is he in contact with them?
没有 但我们假设有联系
Not to our knowledge, but we assume yes.
-有孩子吗？
-两个
Any kids?Two.
最小的几岁？
What's the age of the youngest?
十六岁
Sixteen.
十六岁？
Sixteen?
如果你想发动一场战争
Yeah, if you want to start a war...
先绑架王子
kidnap a prince.
国王就会开战
King will start it for you.
你在中东做过这样的事情
You did this sort of thing in the Middle East.
嗯
Hmm.
你觉得这种策略在这里有用吗？
You think those tactics will work here?
只要你想这么做 先生
If you want it to, sir.
人员部署方面 你得雇用外面的人
Boots on the ground, you're gonna hire on the outside.
包括后勤车辆
And the same goes for your supply train
以及空中支援
and for air support.
我不需要提醒你
And I don't need to remind you
如果他们发现幕后是我们 后果会怎样
what happens if they figure out that it's us.
要讲明白的是
Just to be clear,
你想要让这件事情成功
you want to see this thing through,
那我必须 干肮脏工作
I'm gonna have to get... dirty.
干肮脏工作就是你来这里的原因
Dirty is exactly why you're here.
你需要什么？
What do you need?
一切
Everything.
具有攻击能力的无人机
Drones with attack capability...
你有黑鹰 对吧
You have Black Hawks, right?Mm-hmm.
我要两架 我需要后勤
I want two of those. I need logistics,
与特种作战司令部相容的通讯设备
communications equipment compatible with a SOCOM JCU.
第一阶段 我需要一支突击队
First phase, I need a strike team,
两个狙击手 还有爆破小组
two snipers, I need a demolition team...
你要去乌克兰吗？
Are you going to Ukraine?[CHUCKLES]
兄弟 我有俄罗斯人还在薪水单上
I got Russians on the payroll, brother.
别把我至于这种位置上
Don't put me in that position.
行动位置在哪里？
Where's the coup?
这是一次抽取行动
It's an extraction...
开始是这样
for starters.
我能知道多少？
How much can I know?
兄弟 你不会想知道的
Brother, you don't want to know.
好吧 我不需要知道细节
Well, I don't need specifics,
但我得知道他们要去哪里
but I have to know where they're going.
墨西哥
Mexico.
你一定是来开玩笑的
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
不是针对政府
It's not the government.
而是针对贩毒集团
It's cartel.
财政部在哪里付款？
Treasury cutting the checks?
在巴西的一家叫做力拓的公司
Eh, under a company in Brazil called Rio Verde.
只要一切开始运行
If it's constant action,
我就得负责每月1000万的薪水补给
I'm ten mil a month in payroll and supplies.
这是最少的
At least.
我要1500万的费用和豁免权
I want 150 over cost and immunity.
成交
Done.
恭喜你 现在你可以有个自己的曲棍球队了
Congratulations, you can afford your own hockey team now.
波哥大 哥伦比亚
我在你屋里等你 别他妈开枪打我
在圣诞节买东西会容易些
You'll be easy to shop for at Christmas.
我从不庆祝圣诞节
I don't celebrate Christmas.
好吧 我打赌你今年一定会庆祝
Well, I bet you will this year.
他们做了什么？
What'd they do?
不重要
Doesn't matter.
这次行动没有规则
No rules this time.
你可以放轻松的干
I'm turning you loose.
放多轻松？
How loose?
卡洛斯 雷耶斯
Carlos Reyes.
怎样 够轻松吧？
How's that for loose?
这是你为家人报仇的好机会
It's your chance to get even for your family.
你要帮我们发动一场战争
You're gonna help us start a war.
对谁？
With who?
所有人
Everyone.
墨西哥城
Aah! Aah...
Aah!
戴上
再见了
Adios.
迪亚兹是马塔莫罗斯集团的律师
官方怀疑他被其他贩毒集团杀害
他们担心进一步的报复行动会展开
进而发动新的毒贩之间的战争
等她到家再行动会更好些
This would have been a lot easier taking her in the house.
在街上显得很草率
Could get real sloppy on the street.
草率点更好
Sloppy's good.
草率点让它看起来像是其它贩毒组织干的
Sloppy makes it look like the cartel did it.
好吧 开始行动
All right, let's go.
我要杀了你
你这臭婊子
看什么看？
是她先动手的
She started it.
雷耶斯小姐？
Miss Reyes?
她骂我是妓女 打我耳光 所以我才揍了她
She called me a narco whore and slapped me, so I hit her.
换成你会怎么做？
What would you do?
你
You.
去找护士
Go to the nurse.
不 你哪里也别去
No, you're not going anywhere.
坐下
Sit.
现在我要怎么处理你？
Now what am I going to do with you?
她罪有应得
She deserved what she got.
这地方不是你说了算
It's not your place to do it.
好吧
Fine.
那你去揍她一顿
You beat the shit out of her.
我真应该开除你
I should expel you.
开除啊
Do it.
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
看到什么了？
How we looking?
看到目标了吗？
Got eyes on the prize?
收到
Roger.
目标在后面一辆车上
Prize is in the tail vehicle.
什么情况
怎么没有网路连接了
检查一下你的手机信号
没信号
加速前进
不！
No!
不！不！不！
No! No! No!
告诉你们老板卡洛斯 雷耶斯
这就是马塔莫罗斯集团应得的
-我们去哪里？-直接上飞机
Where we going?Go straight to the plane.
不用管车 我们会处理
Don't worry about the vehicle. We'll take care of it.
好的
All right.
你要开车去购物中心
All right, you're gonna drive that to the mall.
钥匙放在加油盖上 就留在那里
Keys are in the gas flap. You just leave them there.
然后你去看看有什么在等着你
All right. Then you go see what's waiting for you.
柯伯克里斯帝 德州 美国海军机场
-我们接下来去哪里？-5号楼 先生
Where you got us?Building 5, sir.
-你得往左走 -我知道怎么过去
You're gonna take a left.I know where it is.
现在让我们好好看看
Now walk me through what I'm watching here.
这是一张在100英里网格的墨西哥地图
This is a map of Mexico on a hundred-mile grids.
你在这里接到的目标
And you took the subject here.
据推测 雷耶斯有个住所
Speculation is Reyes has a family residence
在蒙特雷附近
somewhere near Monterrey.
墨西哥警方有什么消息？
Has the Mexican police responded yet?
有的 地方 州和联邦警察都到了现场
Yeah, local, state and federal police are all there now.
卫星无法获取手机信号
Satellite cannot pick up cell chatter.
但我们可以锁定目标座标
Okay.Yeah, we can lock coordinates
之后抓取电话号码
to the cell and snag the phone number,
但我们听不到电话内容
but we can't hear the call.
给我墨西哥城房子的卫星信号
Give me a satellite feed of the house in Mexico City.
是的 已切换
Yeah, you got it.
希望这个地方打出电话
What we're hoping for is a call from this location
我们就可以追踪电话
to start a trail.
房子里有家庭成员吗？
Any family members in the house?
没有 只是工作人员
No, just staff.
拥有30个豪宅房间的少女
Teenage girl with her own 30-room mansion.
真希望我是那个少女
I wish I was a teenage girl.
播放现场影像
Pull up the incident site.
看来你把他们都干掉了
It looks like you popped them all.
不对 我们只撂倒一个
No, we only engaged one.
一个是死于车祸 另外两个人被绑起来
One died in the crash, and the other two we tied and left.
冒这么大的风险 为什么？
That's a pretty big risk. Why do that?
想看看他们什么反应
Just to see what they'd do.
倒回去 看看之前的录影
Back it up. Show me earlier.
从我们离开的那时候开始
A minute just after we left.Yeah.
前进一些
Keep going.
从这里开始 很好
All right, there, good.
我们有新的音讯进入监视器手机
We have new audio coming in on the black phone.
收到
Copy that.
电话不是从房子里面打来的
Call is not coming from the house,
是从那个混蛋那里
it's coming from that fucker right there.
即时监听 并找到他
Give me a live feed and find him.
马上
On it.
电话！
Phone!
锁定它
Lock in on it.
好了 现在已锁定
All right, locking now.
数据已连接 这是国王
Data link up.There's the king.
就是这个 开始追踪
There it is. Start tracking.
快点
Come on.
两秒后开始
Tracking on two.
稍等 三秒
Stand by. We got three.
求你不要伤害我
求你了
Por favor.
你想把我怎么样
求你了
Por favor.
如果你放了我
我什么都不会说 我发誓
渴了就自己喝点水
我发誓 求你了
趴下！警察！趴下！
Get down!Police! Get down!
把手举起来 快！
Hands where I can see 'em!Move! Move!
安全！
Clear!
这还有一个人！
We got another one here!
你没事吧？
A-Are you okay?
安全了吗？
Are we clear?
安全！
All clear!
没事的
It's okay.
我们走 没事了
Let's go. It's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
没事了 没事了
It's okay. It's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
我在德州？
Am I in Texas?
是的
Yeah, we are.
你叫什么名字？
What do you want us to call you?
-伊莎贝拉 -伊莎贝拉
Isabel.Isabel.
我要问一些问题
I need to ask you a question.
他们伤害你了吗？
Did they hurt you?
这里是怎么弄的？
What happened here?
我在学校打架了
I got in a fight at school.
我什么时候可以回家呢？
So when do I get to go back home?
我们还需要解决一些问题
Well, we still need to work through some things
确保我们了解所有发生的情况
to make sure we understand all the circumstances
包括你被绑架的情况 好吗？
surrounding your abduction, okay?
你在这里是安全的
But you're safe.
等会儿你就可以回家
So hang in there, we're gonna get you home very soon.
艾丽西亚会照顾你的
Alicia will look after you.
有什么需要的 你就问她
And if you need anything, just ask her.
我们把这女孩放在马塔莫罗斯的地盘中央
We put the girl in the middle of Matamoros territory,
雷耶斯将会开战
and Reyes will start the fireworks.
我们在哪里放下她比较好呢？
What's a good spot where we can leave her?
我们会把她带到蒙德斯的联邦警察局
We'll hold her in a federal police depot in Méndez.
我们很深入马塔莫罗斯地盘
We're deep enough in Matamoros land
如果他们来找她
that they'll have to fight their way out
就必须杀出一条血路
if they come looking for her.
你在哪里找到她的？
Where do I say you found her?
我们突袭了布朗斯维尔的一个安全屋
Oh, say we raided a safe house in Brownsville
在那里找到了她
and found her there.
马塔罗斯贩毒集团在这一带势力非常强大
Matamoros Cartel is very strong in this area.
雷耶斯将很难让他的人通过那里
Reyes will have trouble getting his men through.
他们会让他的人通过的
Ah, they'll let his men through.
撤退是他们的问题
Getting back out will be their problem.
你什么时候带她过境？
When would you bring her across?
既然要让贩毒集团互斗
Well, now that we got the cartels
自然是越早越好
at each other's throats, the sooner the better.
秘密不会持续太久
Secret won't keep long.
在墨西哥没有秘密
Uh, there's no secrets in Mexico.
你觉得我为什么开装甲车？
Why do you think I'm driving armor?
你能帮我清理一下吗？
Can you get me cleared for that?
好的
Will do.
联邦警察会护送你到边境
Federal police will meet you at the border with an escort.
-谢谢 -不客气
-Thanks. -No tienen
不管用任何理由
干掉卡洛斯雷耶斯都是好事
祝你好运 兄弟
还是让我很惊讶
Still amazes me.
这地方的口味
The appetite of this place.
是啊 欢迎来到美国
Yeah, well, welcome to America.
你没事吧？
You all right?
搞屁啊？！
What the fuck?!
你他妈的瞎了眼睛吗？
Hey! Why don't you keep your fucking eyes peeled?
根本分不出他们是不是混帮派
Ah, you can't even tell they're gangbangers anymore.
我有个问题
I've got a problem.
必须天亮前回家 不然我爸会抓狂的
Either be home before dawn or my dad will get mad.
滚一边去 兄弟 不
Oh, get the fuck out, dude, no. No, no, no.
你现在有了新爸爸了 好吧？
You got a new daddy now. All right?
当你去见他时 表现的男人一点
When you meet him, act like a fucking man.
准备好做真男人了 是吧？
You ready to be a man, right?
-好吧 表弟 -好吧
-All right, yes, dude. -All right.
待在这里 等我来接你 好吗？
Just wait here till I come get you, all right?
来吧
Come on.
我叫你去找他 快去
盖勒
这是你美国表哥
来吧 别怕 坐下
-还好吗？
-很好
-你叫什么名字？
-米格尔
我需要一些值得信任的人
别在这给我鬼扯 快去找到他
这些白痴们
33号车需要更多的移民
操
你听说过锦鲤吗？
没有
No. ¿No?
没？我家里有一池子的锦鲤
它们全都很大 五颜六色的
但我最喜欢的还是其中一条大鱼
我叫它圣诞老人 因为它实在太肥了
等我找到那个家伙
我会把她劈成碎片
把她喂给圣诞老人
你不会害怕了吧？
-你会穿越边境 对吧？
-是的
我知道你值得信任
你赚的钱会比你爸一年赚的都多
那就说定了
好的
Sí.
感觉好点吗？
How you feeling?
如果有人早点告诉我一切事情
I'd feel better if someone actually told me
我会感觉好一点
what was going on.
我们要把你交给墨西哥军队
We're turning you over to the Mexican Army.
他们会安排你回到你父亲身边
They'll arrange to take you back to your father.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你需要穿上这个
I'm gonna need you to put this on.
枪支上膛！
Load up!
枪支上膛 出发 ！
Loading up! Heads up!
有七辆墨西哥警车
I have seven Mexican police vehicles
在边境线等候
located at the border checkpoint waiting.
他们正在移动列队
They're moving and forming up
加入你们的车队
in your configuration at this time.
今天可是开车的好天气 是吧？
It's a nice day for a drive, huh?
是啊 真是美好的一天
Ah, beautiful day.
蓝蓝的天 还有大口径武器
Blue skies, large-caliber weapons.
太喜欢走出办公室了
I love getting out of the office.
空中支援 现在什么情况？
Air, how are we looking?
一切都很安全
Clear on both sides.
没看到什么车辆？
You see no vehicles?
除了沙漠 什么都没有
Nothing but desert.
你们很安全
You're clear.
你的视角有多大？
What's your field of view?
每个方向10英里范围
Ten miles in every direction.
墨西哥干员表示 这条路很安全
Mexico Feds said that the road would be clear.
看来他们信守承诺
Looks like they're keeping their word.
好的 收到
All right, copy that.
我们为什么不在边境停下来？
Why weren't we stopped at the border?
因为有特别行动
'Cause I'm special.
我以为你们是警察
I thought you were policemen.
你们是军人
You're soldiers.
是我们救了你 你就不能好好的坐在后面
You know, we saved you-- why don't you just sit back
并心存感激吗？
and be grateful.
奥斯卡一号 公路将在半英里后结束
Oscar-One, paved road ends half a mile ahead.
等等 什么？
Wait, what?
公路还有半英里长结束
Paved road ends in half a klick.
路还没完全铺好
Road isn't paved ahead.
-你带热成像了吗？ -带了 在我包里
You got your thermal?Yeah, in my bag
-包在后面 -你得扶着方向盘 -好的
-In the back; -You gotta take the wheel. -All right.
你拿
Got it.
该死
Oh, shit.
没有比这更简单的
Nothing's ever easy.
我拿到了
I got it.
妈的
Shit.
我依旧看不见
I got no vis.
这混蛋在加速
This fucker's speeding up.
好吧 他们不傻 紧跟着他们
Well, he's not stupid. Stay on his ass.
这泥土路让我很紧张
Dirt roads make me nervous.
空中支援 我看不见东西
Air, I'm blind here.
道路很安全
Road's clear.
左右两边没有任何移动的车辆
No vehicles, no movement, left or right.
好的 什么都没有？
All right, anything?
该死 奥斯一号 你们右边
Shit. Oscar-One, incoming on your right.
空中支援 我什么都看不见
Air, I see nothing. Contact right.
我什么都看不见
I don't see anything.
全都趴下
All down! Down!
卡住了 我被卡住了
Stuck! I'm stuck!
来吧
Aw, come on!
西边 几百公尺处！
West side, hundred meters!
撂倒他！
Take him out!
收到 低头！
Roger that. Heads down!
低头
Heads down!
我们被困住了 我们被困住了
We're stuck. We're stuck.
快走
Go! Go, go!
停火！停火！
Cease fire! Cease fire!
安全！
Clear!
联邦警察 救命
安全
Clear.
放下武器！
Drop your weapon!
那边 各位！
Them, over there.Sir!
散开！
Spread out!
放下武器
不要开枪
放下武器 兄弟！
Put 'em down, guys!
慢慢来
Easy, easy.
!Abajo!Ayuda.
放轻松 各位
Easy, guys, easy.
下来！
Down. Down. !Ayuda!
拜托 我们需要帮助
我们是联邦警察
操！
Fuck!
该死
Shit.
他妈的 墨西哥警察开枪打我？
Fuckin' Mexican police shot me?
你还好吗？
You all right?
妈的
Oh, shit.
我没事 打到防弹衣了
I'm good. It caught the plate.
好的 都没事吧？
All right. We clear?
长官 有警车从南面往这边来了
Sir! We have police vehicles approaching from the south.
五公里外
Five klicks out.
好吧 上车！
All right, load up!
快点 全员上车！
Come on, load up!
她在哪里？
Where is she?
新任务！
New mission!
集合 新任务！
Gather round! New mission!
已经没时间了
Uh... no time for that.
你们继续往北 我去找她
Head north. I'll find her.
好的 我们走
Okay. Go.
三公里外有援军
All right, we got company three klicks out,
从南面赶过来了
coming from the south.
把那辆悍马拖过来
Grab that Humvee, pull this thing out.
快！
Go! Now! Now!
快点 各位 快点！
Come on, guys! Now!
快走 我们走！
Go, go! Let's go!
快走
Let's go! Move it!
拿上这个
Take this.
好的
All right?
到达边境时 发信号给我
Send me a signal when you get to the border,
我们会去接你
we'll come and get you.
好吗？
All right?
走 快 我们走！
Let's go, let's go! Let's move it!
好了 所有人上车！
All right, everyone in their vehicles!
空中支援 我们需要医生在汇合点
Air, we need a medivac from rally point alpha.
联络劳克林47号
Contact 47th med at Laughlin.
收到 奥斯卡一号
Roger that, Oscar-One.
注意你们身后
Be advised, you have police vehicles
有三辆警车从六点钟方向靠近
approaching your six in a Code 3.
好的 收到
Oh, that's great.
六点钟方向有三辆警车快速接近
Police approaching our six fast.
空中支援 我们需要边境通道通畅
Air, we need a lane clear at the border.
谁挡着我 就干掉他
No bullshit. Anybody gets in our way,
我们直接碾过去
we drive right through them.
边境快到了
Border coming up fast. Border.
!Oye!
伊莎贝拉？
Isabel?
不！
No!
上车
Get in.
你会没事的
到底是谁绑架了我？
Who kidnapped me?
你父亲敌人太多
Your father has a lot of enemies.
你是其中之一？
And you're one of them?
是的
Yes, I am.
-你需要缝合伤口 -是啊 很幸运
-You're gonna need stitches. -Yeah. Lucky for me
我明天还得用这条手臂
I'll still need them tomorrow.
阳光小姐在你身后
Miss Sunshine on your six.
该死的星期一 是吧？
Hi. Fuckin' Mondays, huh?
我们能单独聊会儿吗？
Can we go somewhere that's private?
没问题
All right.
-请稍等一下 -女士
Can you give me a sec?Ma'am.
我有可靠的消息来源
My source is with her right now.
她几小时后会回到这里
She'll be back in an hour.
我说的不是这个
That's not what I'm talking about.
不是蓝就是绿 辛西雅
It was a green on blue, Cynthia.
没有别的选择
There was no other option.
你当时想要阿富汗 现在得到了
You wanted Afghanistan, now you got it.
这里不是阿富汗
This isn't Afghanistan.
这是我们的邻国
This is our fucking neighbor!
有5400万美国人在那里有亲戚
There are 54 million Americans with relatives there,
他们坐在那里看好戏
Mm-hmm.and they're all sitting around
福斯新闻播出 墨西哥警察尸横遍野
watching footage of dead Mexican police
警察跟毒贩串通好了
on Fox News.The police were the ambush.
我们别无选择
Oh, yeah, okay.We had no choice.
他们袭击了我们
All...They attacked us.
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
上头对这事已经没兴趣了
doesn't have the stomach for this.
我们被封杀了
He shut us down.
-你说什么？ -我们被封杀了
-What did you say? -We're shut down.
我做好了我的工作 你去做你该做的
I did my fuckin' job. You do yours.
你去跟那个懦夫解释
You sit that fuckin' coward down,
把这一切讲给他听 我们才能赢
and you explain to him-- this is how we win.
他根本不关心赢不赢
He's not worried about winning.
他只担心会不会被弹劾
He's worried about being fucking impeached,
因为你们杀了二十几个墨西哥警察
because you killed two dozen Mexican police.
他们是为雷耶斯卖命的人警察
Who worked for Reyes.
动动脑袋 做好你的事
Spin it. Do your job.
这会巩固我们的立足点
This only strengthens our position.
我们没有立足点 麦特
We don't have a position, Matt.
因为我们根本不该出现在那该死的地方
Because we're not supposed to fucking be there.
你的目标是挑起墨西哥贩毒集团之间的战争
Your objective was to start a war with Mexican cartels,
而不是针对墨西哥政府
not with the Mexican government.
你知道吗？
You know what?
所以说什么都没改变
This-this is why nothing ever changes.
你真以为改变才是目的 真的？
You think change is the goal? Really?
你干太久了 才会相信这套
You've been doing this too long to believe that.
你好 先生 麻烦一下
我们迷路了
不要害怕
我不是坏人
我叫阿加德罗
你叫什么名字？
Sí.
阿杰
我们需要食物和水
还需要一个休息的地方
如果你能帮助我们
我可以付钱给你
她上过电视 她被绑架了
帮帮我 还有她
你怎么会手语？
因为我的女儿
她是聋哑人吗？
是的
抱歉
你们为什么不把她关在墨西哥某处？
Why didn't you hold her someplace in Mexico?
我们在那里没有基础设施 长官
We don't have the infrastructure for that, sir.
几乎不可能保证任务安全
Mission security would be almost impossible.
-这是你的任务吗？-不是 长官
Was this your mission?No, sir.
那你该怎么回答？
Then why are you answering?
格雷夫先生？
Mr. Graver?
我们在那里没有基础设施 长官
We don't have the infrastructure for that, sir.
几乎不可能保证任务安全
Mission security would be almost impossible.
这女孩已经目击了所有行动过程
And this girl was witness to all aspects of the mission,
-对吗？ -不 她只是被绑架了
correct? -No, she was shielded from the kidnapping.
那么那25名墨西哥警察
What about the 25 Mexican police officers
在墨西哥的土地上被杀掉
that were killed, on foreign soil,
她是否目睹了全过程？
all of which she witnessed?
-那些袭击我们的人？ -是的 长官
-The ones who attacked us? -Yes, sir.
她现在在哪里？
Where is she?
我有人会把她带回边境
I have a source bringing her to the border.
现在有具体的位置吗？
Do we have an exact location?
我在问你 福尔辛先生
That question is for you, Mr. Forsing.
我们现在还不知道他们在哪里
We don't know her whereabouts, sir,
不过他有信号器 一旦靠近边境
but he has a beacon-- he'll activate it
他就会启动信号器
as soon as he gets close to the border.
如果他们到的了边境
If they can make it to the border.
这是我们不能冒的风险
Which is a chance we cannot take.
辛西雅
Cynthia.
是的 长官
Yes, sir?
现在由你接管任务
You handle it from here.
我们不能冒险让她落入别人手中
We can't risk her falling into the wrong hands.
信号器一旦被启动
When the beacon's activated,
你们必须要处理掉他们
your team takes them.
明白吗？
You understand?
清理现场
Clean the scene.
我说的清理 各位 是要毫无瑕疵
When I say clean, gentlemen, I mean spotless.
包括你的人
Your operative included.
你知道
Do you know...
他这样做有多难吗？
how hard he was to make?
我朝河中丢根棍子
I could throw a stick across the river
都能打到50个悲伤的父亲
and hit 50 grieving fathers.
再做一次
Make another one.
我办不到
Can't do that.
现在看来是谁最倒胃口
Well, look who doesn't have the stomach for it now.
我替你擦了多少屁股
Oh, who are you to question me
你有何资格来质问我？
after all the shit that I've eaten for you?
我们确认了炸弹攻击者的身份 麦特
We ID'd the other bombers, Matt.
他们是美国公民
They're U.S. citizens.
他们来自纽泽西 什么都没改变
They're from New Jersey.Doesn't change anything.
什么都他妈的改变了！
It changes the fucking narrative!
-这孩子耳聋了吗？
-没有
不一样的世界
我明白了
嘿
Hey.
你找到那个女孩了？
You got the girl?
是的 她现在和我在一起
She's with me now, yeah.
他们要我清理干净
They want me to cut ties.
你必须把她处理掉
You got to get rid of her.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
你说什么？
What are you telling me?
这次不行
Not this one.
帮我带她越境
Help me get her across,
然后再决定怎么处置她
and we can decide what to do with her.
别让我为难
Uh-uh. Don't put me in that situation.
如果他们要清理干净 就已经很为难你了
If they're cutting ties, you're already in that situation.
如果把她留在这里 她会被杀死的
If she stays here, she'll be killed.
帮我带她越境
Help me get her across.
我帮不了你
I can't help you do that.
你做你应该做的
You gotta do what you gotta do.
我再想办法
I'll figure it out.
祝你好运
Good luck.
我得带你去北方
I got to get you north.
看 闪光的就代表你
See, the flashing light is you.
好吗？那条红线
All right? That red line,
就是你的路线
that's your path.
好的 别弄湿了
Okay.Don't get that wet.
注意安全
Keep it safe for a bit.
嘿
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
记住他们是绵羊
They're sheep.
Treat them like it.
把他们当做绵羊
!Rápido!
救命
别管她 继续走！
!Vámonos!
跟上我
我们到了
快点
都快点
沿着小路去公路边
Follow the trail to the road.
有车子在等你
Your ride's waiting.
没事的
It's okay.
上来吧
Come on.
给我报酬更高的工作 我来做
Show me a job that pays better and I'll do it.
你要去哪里 宝贝？
Where are you headed, baby?
带我去特伦顿的杂货店
Get me to the grocery store on Trenton.
我从那里步行离开
I can walk from there.
为什么一个军人懂得用手语？
Why does a soldier know sign language?
我女儿是个聋哑人
My daughter was deaf.
我知道你是谁了
I know who you are.
你是被他们杀死全家人的律师
You're the attorney whose family they killed.
不是 "他们"
Not "they."
我的父亲
My father.
你父亲的手下杀的
A man who worked for him.
为什么？
Why?
为了警告我
To send a message.
现在你要猎杀他们
Now you hunt them...
你不仅仅是要警告
so you won't be a message.
我永远都在警告他们
I will always be a message.
只不过现在警告的方式变了
Only now, the message is different.
边境很难通过吗？
Is the border hard to cross?
可能会
It could be...
对伊莎贝拉 雷耶斯而言
for Isabel Reyes.
从现在起 你的名字叫卡瑞娜
From now on, your name is Carina.
我叫卡瑞娜
你来自瓦哈卡州
如果有人问我是谁
就说你付钱要我假扮你爸爸
为什么不直接说你是我爸爸
因为撒谎会带给你安全
所以现在开始 我们要说些谎话
把你鞋子给我
那是什么？
GPS信号器
万一我们走散了
信号在1993位置被启动了
Signal was activated at 1939,
雷诺萨城东北方
heading northeast of Reynosa.
我派其他部队完成这项任务
I'm sending another team to finish this.
不用 我处理
No. I'll do it.
如果我不处理 他说不定回来连你都杀了
'Cause if I don't, he'll probably come and kill you.
这么多人
这就是现实
-这里的老大呢？
-马上就来
早安 未来的美国佬 感觉如何
谁还没交钱呢？
你吗？
没有
知道多少钱吗？
我们两人 一千元
每人一千
我到了那边还得用钱呢
这没得商量
小孩子得上另一辆车
Oh...
我们得在一起
这是一千块
这是另外一千
那行吧 好的
所有人上蓝色巴士
你们俩 要在一起的
带上孩子 走吧
其他人 先在这里等着
路上有干扰
There's interference on the road.
-车辆有没有标记 是警察吗？-没有标记
-Are the vehicles unmarked or police? -Unmarked.
什么时候抵达？
ETA to target?
25分钟之后
25 minutes.
各位朋友 前面就是天堂了
别动
你带枪了？
是的
站起来
搜一下他
包里还有什么东西？
毒品吗？
不是
所有人下车
快点
瞧瞧我们找到了什么
移民禁止带枪
是他吗？
是他
你几天前是不是去过德州？
没有 没去过
没有？
我的人可不会撒谎 特别是对我
把伊莎贝拉带去我的车上
你到底是想干什么
你是想去对面渡假吗？
不是
我们的处境不太妙
只能透过这种方式越境
我跟女孩说 带她去见她妈妈
你们的人越境会赚很多钱
但也会很危险
都是为了自己和爱的人
如果你伤害那女孩 新的战争就会开始
你们脱不了关系
或者我们可以打个电话 换取所有人安全
这样对大家都好 不用惹任何麻烦
你不是卡洛斯的人吗？
这个你不用管 兄弟
别害怕 我们是来保护你的
你们到底有什么秘密？
不知道
他是我雇用的
来假扮我父亲
你朋友说他是卡洛斯的手下
你父亲的人
嗯？
是的
现在该怎么办呢？
打电话给我的人 让他们联络老大
那就打吧
不！
No! No!
不！不！不！
No! No! No!
不！
No!
那是他吗？还要多久到达？
That's him. ETA?
15分钟
15 minutes.
十分钟到达 我不能让那女孩泄密
Get us there in ten-- I can't have the girl talk.
坐稳了
Hang on back there.
会很颠簸
Gonna get bumpy.
路到尽头了 我的朋友
你会像个畜牲一样死去
死在一个孩子手里
过来 何塞
José.
杀了他
这就是杀手的训练
开枪啊
开枪 你就能变成真正的杀手
我来吧 他还是个孩子
他可以的
勇敢些 别害怕
不！
No!
幸好我们不必这么做
Glad we didn't have to do that.
那女孩怎么办？
What about the girl?
两分钟后到达
Two minutes out.
麦特？
Matt?
基地 目标在车内的具体位置？
Base, what's subject's exact location inside the car?
目标在后排
Subject is back seat,
后排右侧
right side behind the passenger.
目标在后排右侧 绿色行动代码启动
Prize is passenger side, second seat, green Expedition.
交战规则呢？
Rules of engagement?
去他妈的
Fuck it all.
赶尽杀绝
Wipe it clean.
哈维尔 别开枪 做好准备
都站起来 ！
Stand up! Stand up!
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
麦特！
Matt!
你在害死我们！
You're fucking us!
-她说了不留活口！-狗屁
-She said spotless. -Fuck 'em all.
她会列入证人保护计划的
She'll go into witness protection.
坐下
Sit down.
所以你想成为一个杀手
So you wanna be a sicario.
那么我们来谈谈你的未来
Let's talk about your future.